Guide to the Lesbian, Gay, Transgender, Bisexual, and Queer Student Life at Yale University Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Lesbian, gay, transgender, bi-sexual, and queer student life at Yale University collection
1980-2012
RU 1042
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.1
(6 boxes)
This intentionally assembled collection consists of posters and postcards documenting lesbian, gay, transgender, bisexual, and queer student life at Yale, specifically gay pride week events and activities. Also included are posters documenting plays written by William Schwalbe.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 41 (YRG 41), Material documenting Yale student life.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
This intentionally assembled collection consists of posters and postcards documenting lesbian, gay, transgender, bisexual, and queer student life at Yale, specifically gay pride week events and activities. Also included are posters documenting plays written by William Schwalbe.
Bisexuality; College students; Gay liberation movement; Homosexuality; Lesbianism; Transsexualism; Yale University -- Students
- B-GLAD journal, 1988; Accession 2006-A-086
  - B-GLAD journal, 1988 (Box 1)
- Pride Week ephemera, 2007; Accession 2007-A-174
  - Pride at Yale 2007 poster, LGBT Coop (Box 1)
  - Debutante Balls postcards, Yale Cabaret, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Queer authorship panel discussion posters, Sterling Memorial Library, 2007 (Box 1)
- Posters documenting plays of William Schwalbe, 1982-1983; Accession 2009-A-150
  - Cidental, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Twins, 1983 (Box 1)
- LGBTQ Coop records, circa 1980-1982; Accession 2009-A-196
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - News clippings (Box 1)
  - GL Co-operative agenda (Box 1)
  - Ngay and lesbian referral list (Box 1)
  - Yale Pride t-shirt (Box 1)
- The Outlaws banquet program, 2008; Accession 2010-A-008
  Biographical / Historical
  The Outlaws are the Yale Law School association of gay law students.
  Scope and Contents
  Program from first annual banquet held in Sterling Memorial Library's Linonia and Brothers (L&B) room.
  - The Outlaws banquet program, 2008 (Box 1)
- Yale Pride 2012 posters, Accession 2012-A-083 (Box 1)